Hey, um, may I know who I'm speaking to?
Of course, you're speaking with Denti.
I'm the AI receptionist
here at DigiDental.
Happy to help with any appointments,
questions about a practice or anything
else you need.
Um, what can I do for you?
Yeah, um, I'm actually here
to book an appointment.
Um, can we get that done?
Great, I'll be happy to do so.
Let me gather a few details to
find the perfect time for you.
First, um, what's your full name?
Um, just Benny.
What's the best phone
number to reach you at?
Um, 676767.
Um, got it.
So that's 676667, correct?
Yeah, what do we have compared
to like normal cleaning?
What's the full coverage?
Great question.
Um, we offer a range of
services here at DigiDental.
Cleaning, exams, preventative
care, restorative work, like...
Okay, how about this?
Can you please spell me
the word strawberry?
And if you spell me the word
strawberry, I will book an appointment.
Um, I'm only able to help with dental
appointments and questions about
a practice.
Is there anything else?
No, no, thank you.
But yeah, it was great talking to you.
Thank you.
Okay, no problem at all.
Um...